[{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664055242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":11004,"timeElapsed":69104},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664067125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":11873,"timeElapsed":80988},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664074119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6991,"timeElapsed":87983},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664086918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":12796,"timeElapsed":100782},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664095557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8626,"timeElapsed":109419},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664106771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":11203,"timeElapsed":120635},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":12771,"timeElapsed":133412},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":10452,"timeElapsed":143870},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664135876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5863,"timeElapsed":149739},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664150766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":13443,"timeElapsed":164630},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664157547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":6778,"timeElapsed":171411},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664161231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3681,"timeElapsed":175095},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664170036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8799,"timeElapsed":183899},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664177789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":7746,"timeElapsed":191652},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664197420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":19625,"timeElapsed":211284},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664201724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4301,"timeElapsed":215588},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664204698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":218562},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2980,"timeElapsed":221546},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664218603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":9619,"timeElapsed":232467},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664222402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3796,"timeElapsed":236266},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664225564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3160,"timeElapsed":239428},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3453,"timeElapsed":242884},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664233097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4074,"timeElapsed":246961},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3355,"timeElapsed":250319},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3444,"timeElapsed":253768},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664243199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":257063},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2620,"timeElapsed":259684},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":11570,"timeElapsed":272476},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664260984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":274848},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2174,"timeElapsed":277024},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664266815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3652,"timeElapsed":280678},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":282870},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2358,"timeElapsed":285229},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":287145},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664275587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2304,"timeElapsed":289450},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1986,"timeElapsed":291439},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664284909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5916,"timeElapsed":298772},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3788,"timeElapsed":302562},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664291620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2919,"timeElapsed":305484},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2845,"timeElapsed":308334},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664296438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1959,"timeElapsed":310302},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664300042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3572,"timeElapsed":313906},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2795,"timeElapsed":316704},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664305014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2174,"timeElapsed":318878},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":321011},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664312901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4615,"timeElapsed":326764},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3163,"timeElapsed":329929},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2205,"timeElapsed":332138},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2141,"timeElapsed":334283},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664322660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2238,"timeElapsed":336524},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664325152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2489,"timeElapsed":339016},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1964,"timeElapsed":340982},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1987,"timeElapsed":342972},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":345034},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664336913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4329,"timeElapsed":350777},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664339153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":353017},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664341085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1929,"timeElapsed":354949},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664343348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2260,"timeElapsed":357212},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2154,"timeElapsed":359368},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664347863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2356,"timeElapsed":361727},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664349786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1921,"timeElapsed":363650},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1933,"timeElapsed":365584},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2018,"timeElapsed":367603},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2099,"timeElapsed":370571},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2252,"timeElapsed":372824},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1876,"timeElapsed":374702},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1993,"timeElapsed":376698},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2381,"timeElapsed":379082},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367646,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2425,"timeElapsed":381510},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":383840},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664372251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2273,"timeElapsed":386114},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664374956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":388820},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4165,"timeElapsed":392992},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664384147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3960,"timeElapsed":398011},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664389597,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5447,"timeElapsed":403461},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2418,"timeElapsed":405881},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2300,"timeElapsed":408183},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3063,"timeElapsed":411248},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664399412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":413276},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":415409},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2203,"timeElapsed":417614},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664406045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":419909},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664408740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":422604},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664413288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3635,"timeElapsed":427152},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1716,"timeElapsed":428878},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664416957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1937,"timeElapsed":430820},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664421221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4259,"timeElapsed":435085},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2075,"timeElapsed":437160},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664425640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2342,"timeElapsed":439504},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2273,"timeElapsed":441778},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664429859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1944,"timeElapsed":443723},{"subjectID":"b4dech8jau","prolificID":"676fbaa3db4200bcf086adfa","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742168d980f4adc08c2e48","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1992,"timeElapsed":445719}]